Personal Information

- Pie de Boer
- **4** 17 December 1996
- **⋒** Maastricht
- Outch

Pie de Boer

Graduate - Data Science and Artificial Intelligence (BSc)

Contact Enthusiastic and creative graduate from Maastrick

Enthusiastic and creative graduate from Maastricht University with a strong interest in machine learning, signal processing, and generative Al. I possess excellent interpersonal skills and a solid technical mindset, thriving in both collaborative settings and individual research projects. In my spare time, I explore computer topics such as virtual machines, emulators, and Linux, delve into audio engineering, and engage in strength training.

- ★ 10715, Berlin
- **1** +31618928452
- piedeboer96@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/pie-de-boer-6b6663265/
- nttp://github.com/piedeboer96

Competences

Programming Languages

(Advanced): Python, Java, MATLAB (Intermediate): C++, Clojure, R, SQL, Bash

Stack

Google Cloud, Git, Unix, PyTorch, TensorFlow, Jupyter Notebook, Scikit-Learn, Homebrew, and more.

Group Projects

3D Bin Packing

Golf Simulator

Chess Engine

Multi Modal Assistant (Text, Speech and Vision)

Highlighted Courses



Mathematical Modeling

Numerical Mathematics

Data Analysis

Robotics and Embedded Systems

Simulation and Statistical Analysis

Education

■ Data Science and Artificial Intelligence

Maastricht University, Maastricht | 2021 - 2024

Completed (180 ECTS)

Thesis: Conditional Diffusion Models for ECG Signal Denoising (8.5/10.0)

- ~ Trained on Google Cloud and PyTorch.
- ~ Outperforming traditional signal processing methods found in MATLAB.

GPA: 8.28/10.0

Chemistry

Utrecht University, Utrecht | 2016 - 2017

Completed first year (60 ECTS)

GPA: 7.48/10.0

■ VWO (Atheneum)

Bonnefantencollege HAVO/VWO, Maastricht | 2009 - 2016

Profile: Nature & Technology and Nature & Health

Experience

Rabobank (& Maastricht University)

Research Project | 2023 - 2024

Half year research project where I was responsible for improving the quantum approach for their portfolio optimization using Python and D-Wave API working with actual quantum hardware. Weekly contact with senior data scientist and close contact with previous researcher from TNO.

Self-Employed

Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry Tutor | 2019 - Present

Tutored Dutch high school students in core science topics, from HAVO 3 to final exam classes. At peak times, assisted up to seven students per week.

Additional Skills

English (C1) - German (B2) - Dutch (Native)

Maria la Cambana de la Cambifica